{
    "id": "f8738ab21fcc44e38c05aa5e75d7ebd6",
    "title": "Change Into Active Voice",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was cheated by her friends. Her friends ……………………….. her.",
            "description": "Was cheated is the passive form of cheated.",
            "answers": [
                "have cheated",
                "cheated",
                "cheat"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04543fc68b2840b6a743bf1068b9191f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man was bitten by the dog. The dog ………………………. the man.",
            "description": "Was bitten is the passive form of bit. ",
            "answers": [
                "bitten",
                "bite",
                "bit"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "77eaa32963c7473f97f51cd0fe6767b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been promoted. They …………………………….. her.",
            "description": "Has been promoted is the passive form of has/have promoted. ",
            "answers": [
                "promoted",
                "have promoted",
                "were promoted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c2b7368cda9c4118a10bf198f1e9a114"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was inspired by his speech. His speech …………………………. me.",
            "description": "Was inspired is the passive form of inspired. ",
            "answers": [
                "was inspired",
                "inspired",
                "had inspired"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eaea2c059fcf4ae0a54454d69760f1e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The road is being repaired. They ………………………….. the road.",
            "description": "Is being repaired is the passive form of are/is repairing. ",
            "answers": [
                "have repaired",
                "are repairing",
                "are repaired"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b314e107282e4102980c957d35bbc196"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will be punished for this. They ……………………………… you.",
            "description": "Will be punished is the passive form of will punish. ",
            "answers": [
                "will be punishing",
                "will punish",
                "will have punished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f7d686db6964d58b0d59315825d89d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flowers were being plucked by the child. The child ………………………….. the flowers.",
            "description": "Were being plucked is the passive form of were/was plucking. ",
            "answers": [
                "plucked",
                "had plucked",
                "was plucking"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6dee5a99a27e4f1d818fa732ad5c404d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been informed of the accident. We …………………………. him of the accident.",
            "description": "Has been informed is the passive form of has/have informed. ",
            "answers": [
                "informed",
                "have informed",
                "had informed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a0c72af7afd4537afa8f23bb8ebfdec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The suspected are being questioned by the police. The police ……………………………… the suspected.",
            "description": "Are being questioned is the passive form of is/are questioning. ",
            "answers": [
                "questioned",
                "are questioning",
                "have questioned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43b9f80e656948ada61857c2dcf3cea6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tables and chairs are made by carpenters. Carpenters ………………………. tables and chairs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are making",
                "make",
                "had made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "969d9c5aef84477c8305f891ddb9b065"
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured were being treated by the doctors. The doctors ………………………… the injured.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were treated",
                "were treating",
                "have treated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f04da231ec9447e1bb95dfaee6d35cae"
        },
        {
            "question": "The letter was posted in the morning. I …………………………… the letter in the morning.",
            "description": "Was posted is the passive form of posted.",
            "answers": [
                "posted",
                "have posted",
                "had posted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ebf41aa9953c4bf793917b9146ba4a5f"
        }
    ]
}